[{"id": 288, "question": "BEIJING - China will build a nation-wide network within three to five years to monitor the impact of air pollution on health, a latest step to deal with a _ smog crisis in big cities, an official said. A total of 43 monitoring spots will be set up in 16 provinces and municipalities frequently engulfed by smog so as to facilitate research on air pollutants in different regions, the impact on the health of vulnerable groups and the study of related diseases, said Xu Dongqun, an official with the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention. With funds allocated by the central government, the study will provide reference for preventive efforts to reduce the PM 2.5, Xu said. Thick and dangerous smog have hit 17 provinces and municipalities with a population of 600 million this year. One o...\n\nQ: China will build a nation-wide network in order to  _  .", "options": ["monitor the impact of air pollution on health", "improve air quality", "improve air pollution", "increase the PM 2.5"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1867, "question": "My father always told me never to ever reveal my true opinions towards other people unless such opinions are positive. He said this is the \"Chu Shi Zhe Xue\", the philosophy of dealing with social network. It seems that everybody here just follows this philosophy very, very well. I would say that if I were given true friendship I would definitely treasure it with my greatest care. If I really regard someone as my close friend, I would never leave her alone whenever she's in need, either financially or mentally. And I always believe, as long as I treat people with whole-hearted honesty, I would have some rewards--at least, just ONE true friend of the same gender. Sometimes I just miss my friends in China. Perhaps when we became friends, we were still young, too young to have been polluted by...\n\nQ: The writer mostly expresses that she feels   _   in this passage.", "options": ["happy", "homesick", "lonely", "alone"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1511, "question": "Going green seems to be a fad for a lot of people these days.Whether that is good or bad,we can't really say, but for the two of us, going green is not a fad but a life style. On April 22,2011,we decided to be green every single day for an entire year. This meant doing 365 different things, and it also meant challenging ourselves to go green beyond the easy things. Rather than recycle and reduce our energy, we had to think of 365 diffenent things to do and this was no easy task. With the idea of going green every single day a year,Our Greean Year started. My wife and I decided to educate people about how they could go green in their lives and hoped we could show people all green things that could be done to help the environment. We wanted to push the message that every little bit helps. Ov...\n\nQ: What might be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Going green", "Protecting the planet", "Keeping Open-Minded", "Celebrating Our Green Year"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3104, "question": "When I was 18, I had a motorbike accident that put me in a coma for three months. The doctors said there was little chance of my coming out of it, but my identical twin, Marcus, didn't believe them and carried on talking to me. My first words when I came to myself were, \"Hello, Marcus. \"Even though I had no memory of my own name, or that the woman crying at my bedside was my mother, I knew Marcus immediately; it was like a genetic memory. just felt close to him. As weeks went by, I still could remember nothing before the accident. Marcus was the only person I could relate to. I had to relearn everything, and Marcus helped me. Because of my twin I wasn't scared of having lost my memory; I believed everything he said. He became my memory, telling me about my school, friends, previous girlfri...\n\nQ: According to the text, the author   _   .", "options": ["felt very close to Marcus when he first woke up", "didn't get his memories back until months later", "had been very popular before the accident", "remembered nothing but his own name when he first woke up"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 550, "question": "Elena Kagan has reached a lifelong goal:becoming a Justice on the United States Supreme Court.The U.S. Senate confirmed Kagan on Thursday by a vote of 6337.She replaces Justice John Paul Stevens,who retired in June. Kagan will take a sacred oath to uphold the Constitution of the United States on Saturday at a swearingin ceremony.The new Justice will bring the number of women sitting on the nation's highest court to three.Kagan joins Justices Ruth Bader Ginsburg and Sonia Sotomayor--all three New Yorkers. Kagan is the fourth woman in history to sit on the Supreme Court.Justice Sandra Day O'Connor was the first female Justice.She was appointed by President Ronald Reagan and served from 1981 to 2006. Kagan,who is 50 years old,is the second Justice appointed by President Barack Obama.(He appoi...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the text?", "options": ["To take the place of an old Justice,a Justice was elected by the Senate.", "There will be four women working in the United States Supreme Court.", "Kagan will take a sacred oath before taking part in the election.", "No one but a New Yorker can be a Justice of the Supreme Court."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 247, "question": "Worn by the rich and famous around the world and now a $799.04 million-a-year enterprise , Ugg boots have come a long way since their 1973 creation--designed to keep surfers' feet warm in cold Australian conditions. Twenty-eight years after selling the rights to his woollen-lined creation, Aussie Ugg boot inventor Shane Stedman says he has no regrets though missing out on a great footwear fortune . A lifelong surfer, Mr. Stedman, now 69, who lives at beachside Mona Vale in Sydney, said his invention grew from need. \"The sea is bloody cold in the Aussie winter...I used to wear football jerseys to keep them (feet) warm\", Mr. Stedman said. But his sheepskin invention soon solved the problem and Mr. Stedman went on to spend a decade selling the sturdy boots, until 1983 when he sold the rights ...\n\nQ: The Ugg inventor sold the rights to the Ugg boots to   _  .", "options": ["make more money", "pay off his debts", "keep his hobby of surfing", "help improve the US company"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 38, "question": "A rare butterfly has been discovered in Britain for the first time in 60 years,having moved from Eastern Europe.The only previous record of a wild yellow-legged Tortoiseshell in Britain was in 1953,when it was seen just once in Sevenoaks,Kent.Several weeks ago,there were already four confirmed sightings,along the East coast in Norfolk,Suffolk and Kent,and six further reports of the butterfly in coastal areas. Conservationists are very excited about the sightings,which are rare in the butterfly world. The butterflies are thought to have flown on easterly winds across Europe in the last few weeks.The large and colourful insect mainly lives in Eastern Europe.In recent years,it has spread into Scandinavia and its number increases rapidly during warm weather.Also known as the Scarce Tortoiseshe...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the text?", "options": ["Butterflies are quite rare in Britain.", "Butterflies like travelling frequently.", "A rare butterfly appeared in Britain.", "The butterfly world changed a lot."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1210, "question": "For almost two months Dominic York, a 23-year-old hairdresser, wandered about hospitals all night, wearing a white coat and pretending he was a doctor. Yesterday he proudly claimed in court that despite his complete lack of medical experience or qualifications, he had saved several people's lives. He had even been allowed to assist a surgeon during an emergency operation on a patient who was about to die on something she had swallowed. \"I watched one of those TV dramas about a hospital and suddenly I felt like playing one of the roles myself. So I put on a white jacket and a stethoscope and walked around one of the biggest hospital in London. At first I just watched. Once you learn how doctors talk to patients, nurses and others doctors, it's easy to take people in,\" he said. One of the pa...\n\nQ: York learned how to behave like a doctor by    _   .", "options": ["watching other doctors work", "talking to doctors and nurses", "getting some training and experience", "observing doctors while he was a patient"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 118, "question": "Winter is the time of year when people feel very blessed. This isn't because people feel thankful for the cold weather, nor because the important festivals---Christmas or Spring Festival---offer an excuse to celebrate. In fact, \"Bless you!\" is a common response if someone sneezes, a symptom of catching a cold or the flu. Colds and the flu are the most common illnesses of autumn and winter as the weather gets colder. Viruses cause them. If you get one you will feel annoyed, but it is not usually serious. The flu is spread from person to person when we come into contact with a person with the virus. We get the virus on our hands and then we touch our noses and our mouths. We can pass on the flu before we realize we have it. You can infect others one day before symptoms develop and for up to ...\n\nQ: How many ways are mentioned in the passage to stop you from catching the flu?", "options": ["6", "5", "7", "3"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1696, "question": "These days,when about 10.3 million.Americans are jobless and countless mole worry they will be,lovers of yoga are eager to keep peace by twisting their bodies. \"People want to do something relaxing and physically active.My experience is that attendance In classes gone significantly up in the past few months,\"said yoga instructor David,who turned to teaching yoga when his advertising jobs dried up in the recession of 2001.He admitted his private custoIlll~I'8 have fallen off a bit,but \"generally,my long--term private clients are financially well-off and eager to recommend me to their friends.\" \"We've added yoga classes,\"said Nicole Moke,spokeswoman for the fitness centers.\"We add classes every January.\" And if the attack of hard times should fall upon their weft-heeled member ship? \"We've a...\n\nQ: From the passage we can see_.", "options": ["the jobless are eager to practice yoga", "people want to hunt for jobs by practicing yoga", "those practicing yoga don't worry about employment", "those practicing yoga want to seek peace in the hard times"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1352, "question": "A jobless man applied for the position of \"office boy\" at Microsoft. The HR manager interviewed him and then watched him cleaning the floor as a test. \"You are employed,\" he said. \"Give me your e-mail address and I'll send you the application to fill in, as well as date when you may start. \" The man replied, \"But I don't have a computer, neither an e-mail. \" \"I'm sorry,\" said the HR manager. \"If you don't have an e-mail, that means you do not exist. And who doesn't exist cannot have the job. \" The man left with no hope at all. He didn't know what to do, with only ten dollars in his pocket. He then decided to go to the supermarket and buy 10kg tomatoes. He then sold the tomatoes from door to door. In less than two hours, he succeeded to double his capital. He repeated the operation three ti...\n\nQ: The man can be described as   _  .", "options": ["helpful and considerate", "positive and generous", "smart and hardworking", "stubborn and unselfish"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1901, "question": "Students usually have two long holidays a year, but have you heard elephants have holidays? The Indian elephants from a temple are sent on a north-long holiday with massages and baths to relax. The 64 elephants will be fed with a lot of food, enough for them to put on 700~800 pounds. A temple veterinarian said that those Indian elephants would be treated after spending a month walking on roads, living on leaves and bananas and giving shows during lots of temple festivals. Their daily diet includes special rice and other special food, which are very _ and can make them healthy and strong. All of these are made by professional people. This treatment will also calm them down ahead of a busy work schedule in upcoming events later in the year where they are the main attractions. The special hol...\n\nQ: The Indian elephants can have a   _   holiday.", "options": ["day's", "week's", "month's", "year's"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2034, "question": "Many adults in the United States can remember crying the nursery rhyme in the street \"Hot cross buns!\" But only a few people realize this was an early form of advertising. Written advertisements probably began with hieroglyphics more than three thousand years ago, but only a few people could read these symbols. So merchants made signs with pictures or hung their tools over their doors to identify their businesses. In the time of the Roman Empire, wall paintings were a popular form of advertisement. An ad for a play, or some other performance was painted on part of a building or on a wall around a city. People often advertised a house for rent or a freshwater bath in this way, too. Today, large wall signs are still used for outdoor advertising. But outdoor advertising is only a small fracti...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the original form of advertising?", "options": ["Signs with pictures", "Wall signs", "Street crying", "Wall painting"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2280, "question": "It was 1961 and I was in the fifth grade. My marks in school were miserable and, the thing was, I didn't know enough to really care. My older bother and I lived with Mom in an ugly multi-family house in Detroit. We watched TV every night. The background noise of our lives was gunfire and horses' hoofs from \"Wagon Train\" or \"Cheyenne\", and laughter from\"I Love Lucy\", or\"Mister Ed\".After supper, we'd lie on Mom's bed and stare for hours at the TV screen. But one day Mom changed our world forever. She turned off the TV. Our mother had only been able to get through third grade. But, she was much brighter and smarter than we boys know at the time. She had noticed something in the suburban houses where she cleaned books. So she came home one day, switched off the TV, sat us down and explained th...\n\nQ: The author began to love books for the following reasons EXCEPT that   _  .", "options": ["he began to see something in his mind", "he could visualize what he read in his mind", "he could go back to read the books again", "he realized that books offered him new experience"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3318, "question": "With five breakout games, Jeremy Lin has become the NBA's newest star. In the New York Knicks' 92-85 won over the Los Angles Lakers last Saturday, Lin had a career-high 38 points.A day later, he led the Knicks to their fifth victory, 100-98 to Minnesota Timberwolves.In his previous games, Lin, 23, had 23 points against the Washington, 25 points against New Jersey and 28 against Utah in his first start. Lin is smart.Before graduating from high school in California, he had sent his application to all the Ivy League Schools .He only got into Harvard and Brown, and he chose Harvard.In 2010, Lin graduated with a degree in economics. Lin is the first Chinese-American player in the NBA.He was born in the US and his family is Asian.Although not born in China, Lin has attracted nearly all Yao Ming'...\n\nQ: In which team did Lin start his career in NBA?", "options": ["the New York Knicks.", "The Golden State Warriors.", "Minnesota Timberwolves.", "The Los Angles Lakers."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 799, "question": "We all use money every day. It is essential because we can pay money for whatever we want.Money is recognized as banknotes and coins. However,many years ago people couldn' t go to the shop and buy what they wanted.They had to get what they wanted through the barter trade .It was really difficult,for the barter often depended on coincidence of wants.For example,the seller of grain has to find a buyer who wants to buy grain and who also could offer something the seller wants to buy.And one more example,if a wheat farmer needs what a fruit farmer produces,a direct exchange is impossible because seasonal fruit would spoil before the grain harvest.The solution is to trade fruit for wheat indirectly through a third intermediate commodity ,such as cattle,salt,shells,wine.However,commodity money h...\n\nQ: What do we know about the early coins?", "options": ["They usually had large value.", "They were first used in Greece.", "They still had many disadvantages.", "People didn' t like the metal currency."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2491, "question": "Actress Hayden Panettiere recently got into trouble with Japanese fishermen as she tried to stop them from killing dolphins. The 18-year-old star with some other surfers sailed out to reach the dolphins in order to stop them from being driven into a nearby pool and killed, but the six surfers, from Australia and the United States, were stopped by a fishing boat before they could reach them. The fishermen blocked their way with a boathook . It was an ugly, unfriendly and life-threatening struggle before the surfers were forced to return to the beach. It is believed that the dolphins were later taken into a pool and killed. Panettiere, who is a brave surfer and loyal animal protector, made up her mind to save the dolphins of Japan and said, \"It was really frightening. Some of us were hit by ...\n\nQ: From Paragraph 3, we can learn that Panettiere    _   .", "options": ["was really frightened and sad", "succeeded in saving the dolphins", "cried when they were hit by the boathook", "didn't like the Japanese fishermen"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3092, "question": "How's your relationship with your dad? It can be easy to let walls build up between you during the teen years. But by taking several simple steps, you can help improve the relationship between the two of you--even without great efforts. Here are a few quick tips. Talk it out. Communication is key to any friendship. Open your mouth and let your dad know what's on your mind. Give him a chance to get to know you. Listen up. Your dad's lived more life than you have. Believe it or not, he's probably been there and can help you get through the pressures and struggles. Ask how he dealt with school, girls or temptations . Then pay attention. Take some time. It can be hard for us kids to talk about what really matters. But spending time together can build the relationship, and create chances to tal...\n\nQ: \"When temperatures rise\" means  _  .", "options": ["when it is too hot", "when teenagers have a fever", "when fathers fall ill", "when disagreements get worse"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 24, "question": "A couple who held hands at breakfast every morning even after 70 years of marriage have died 15 hours apart. Helen Felumlee, died at 92 on April 12. Her husband, 91-year-old Kenneth Felumlee, died the next morning. The couple's eight children say the two had been inseparable since meeting as teenagers, once sharing the bottom of a bunk bed on a ferry rather than sleeping on night apart. They remained deeply in love until the very end, even eating breakfast together while holding hands, said their daughter, Linda Cody. \"We knew when one went, the other was going to go,\" she said. According to Cody, about 12 hours after Helen died, Kenneth looked at his children and said, \"Mon's dead.\" He quickly began to fade, surrounded by 24 of his closest family members and friends when he died the next ...\n\nQ: How many jobs did Kenneth get?", "options": ["Four.", "Three.", "Two.", "One."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1285, "question": "When looking for love, people may go to some extreme lengths. They might go on blind dates set up by family and friends. They might write personal ad to place in newspapers. Or they might use a computer to help them in their search for a soul mate by joining an online dating service. Some people have even tried to find their perfect match through game shows on television. Many of these TV dating shows, including The Bachelor andWho Wants to Marry Multimillionaire?, have proved to be popular, with millions of viewers watching each week to find out which of the contestants will find true love. Of all these game shows, perhaps the one with the most unexpected ending was Mr. Right, which was shown in England in 2002. On the show, a bachelor, thirty-five-year-old Lance Gerrard-Wright, dated fif...\n\nQ: In Stevie Wonder's song, what is he comparing himself to?", "options": ["A blind man", "A groom", "A letter", "A baby"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 435, "question": "Health insurance can be very expensive. Some working people do not make enough money to pay for it. In the US there is a program called Healthy Families. This program offers people health insurance at a low cost. Families are charged about $7.00 a month for every child, and $10.00 for every adult. It costs much less than any other kind of health insurance. Having health insurance is very important. With this insurance, people can see a doctor when they are sick or hurt. The program is not expensive at all, but many people are still not enrolling in it. People say that it still costs too much money. They need all of their money to pay for things like food and rent . It would be great if everyone could have health insurance. People are working hard to come up with ways to make this happen. O...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["health insurance at a low cost", "the Healthy Families Program", "the cost of health insurance[", "the benefits of health insurance"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 274, "question": "This year, some twenty-three hundred teenagers from all over the world will spend about ten months in their US homes. They will attend US schools, meet US teenagers, and form impressions of the real America. At the same time, about thirteen hundred American teenagers will go to other countries to learn new languages and gain a new understanding of the rest of the world. Here is a two-way students exchange in action. Fred, nineteen, spent last year in Germany with George's family. In turn, George's son Mike spent a year in Fred's home in America. Fred knew little German when he arrived, but after two months' study, the language began to come to him. School was completely different from what he had expected --- much harder. Students rose respectfully when a teacher entered the room. They too...\n\nQ: The exchange programme is mainly to   _  .", "options": ["help teenagers in other countries know the real America", "send students in America to travel in Germany", "let students learn something about other countries", "let teenagers learn new languages"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1026, "question": "Home to me means a sense of familiarity and nostalgia . It's fun to come home. It looks the same. It smells the same. You'll realize what's changed is you. Home is where we ran remember pain, live, and some other experiences; We parted here; My parents met here; I won three championships here. If I close my eyes, I can still have a clear picture in mind of my first home. I walk in the door and see a brown sofa surrounding a low glass-top wooden table. To the right of the living room is my first bedroom. It's empty, but it's where my earliest memories are. There is the dining room table where I celebrated birthdays, and where I cried on Halloween-when I didn't want to wear the skirt my mother made for me. I always liked standing on that table because it made me feel tall and strong. If I si...\n\nQ: What can be learned from the passage?", "options": ["The old furniture is still in the author's fist bedroom.", "The author can still visit her first physical home in Los Angeles.", "The author's favorite room in her first home is the dining room.", "Many people of the author's age can still find their first physical homes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3366, "question": "One day, I was studying at home . Suddenly, there was a loud noise. I went out of my house to see what had happened . What I saw made me scared. A building in my neighborhood was on fire. Some people were using water to put out the fire; others were rushing towards the building to help put out the fire. The building had three floors. The fire started on the first floor. Soon, it spread to the second floor. There were some people on the second floor at that time. Their lives were in danger. A few people jumped out of the window. Luckily, they only got small injuries. Those who were still on the second floor were just crying for help. The people outside didn't know how to help the people inside to get out. Firefighters arrived at last. They fought the fire bravely. Water pipes were used and ...\n\nQ: _  put out the fire in the end.", "options": ["The firefighters and the people inside the building", "The people on the second floor", "The people in the street", "The firefighters"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2295, "question": "Guide dogs are going to be available for the children who are unable to see normally in the UK for the first time, as the age limit is to be removed. The Guide Dogs for the Blind Association is to begin training dogs to help blind people under the age of 16. The association says too many youngsters with impaired eyesight are lacking in independence. They have only a limited social life because of their disability. Giving some of them guide dogs at a younger age is intended to help them to widen their range of activities and to improve their sense of self-confidence and independence. Guide dogs for these teenagers will begin to be provided from next year. There has been an experimental project to test the use of guide dogs with younger people. Charlotte, aged 14, was among the youngest guid...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that owning guide dogs  _  .", "options": ["may meet with difficulties sometimes", "is beneficial to blind children's development", "became possible in the UK recently", "is quite universal in the UK"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3484, "question": "Mr. Briggs got a job with an insurance company after he left school and went around visiting people in their homes to sell them life insurance. One day, after he had been working for the company for about a year, the insurance manager sent for him and said, \"Mr. Briggs, I have been looking at your record as a salesman with our company, and there is one thing that surprises me about it. Why have you been selling insurance only to people over 95 years old, and why have you been giving them such generous conditions? You'll ruin our company if you go on like that. \" \"Oh, no, sir,\" answered Mr. Briggs at once, \"Before I started work, I looked at the figures for deaths in this country during the past ten years, and I can tell you that few people die at the age of 95. \"...\n\nQ: Before he worked in an insurance company, what was Mr. Briggs?  _", "options": [". He was a worker.", "He was an official.", "He was a student.", "He was a businessman."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1868, "question": "I recall a moment that I experienced with my dad when I was twenty-one. I was going to college and living with a couple of friends in Chicago. When the car I was using died, my dad, realizing that I needed transportation to get to work and to school, was good enough to lend me the money for a used car. Shortly after I bought it, my parents drove down to San Diego for the winter. Before they left, my dad gave me some of his bank deposit slips with clear and detailed instructions to put one hundred dollars of my earnings, every payday, into their savings account while they were gone. At that time of my life, I was not yet clear about what were the most important problems that I had to attend to first. I dismissed our agreement as nothing important and continued to spend my money as fast as I...\n\nQ: The writer bought a second-hand car because   _  .", "options": ["he was going to college", "he was living with some friends", "he was working while studying", "his parents wanted to go to San Diego"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1849, "question": "Table manners are very different in every country. For example, when you are in England you must not lift your soup plate to your mouth. This is very impolite. But when you are in Japan this is completely normal. Lifting your plate to your mouth in Japan is a traditional way of drinking your soup. And also in Japan you don't have to worry about making a noise when you drink it. It just shows that you really like the food! But it is not the same in Britain, so you shouldn't make a noise when eating there. In Britain, people don't put their hands or arms on the table during the meal. But in Mexico, guests keep their hands on the table all the time. In fact, you should watch what your hands do very carefully. In Arab countries, it is impolite when you eat with your left hand, so don't do it! ...\n\nQ: How does the text mainly develop?", "options": ["By giving examples.", "By explaining reasons.", "By following the order of time.", "By following the order of importance."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2744, "question": "Occasionally, my father came back drunk. Late at night, he beat on the door, pleading to my mother to open it .He was on his way home from drinking, gambling, or some combination thereof, misspending money that we could have used and wasting time that we desperately needed. It was the late-1970s. My parents were separated. My mother was now raising a group of boys on her own. My father spouted off about what he planned to do for us, buy for us.In fact, he had no intention of doing anything. As a father who was supposed to love us, in fact, he lacked the understanding of what it truly meant to love a child--or to hurt one. To him, this was a harmless game that kept us excited and begging. In fact, it was a cruel, corrosive lie. I lost faith in his words and in him. I wanted to stop caring, ...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Remembrances of my father", "Father and son", "My boy", "The past days"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1264, "question": "Have you ever stood side by side with an elephant and touched its ear or its long nose? A marvelous opportunity is offered here for you to experience working with these giant animals. The daily highlight is the walk from the elephant orphanage down to the river to bathe the elephants. Imaging what an amazing fun it is to watch an entire herd splashing around and rolling in the river just feet in front of you! This opportunity is available through a programme designed for visitors and volunteers to work in the world-famous government-run elephant orphanage in Pinnawela, Sri Lanka. The orphanage is regarded as one of the largest centers of its kind in the world, with one of the most successful captive breeding programmes for Asian elephants. Pinnawela Orphanage is situated in the hills of ce...\n\nQ: Mahouts are probably people who_.", "options": ["train elephants", "bathe elephants", "care for elephants", "drive elephants"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2392, "question": "Every child has written their names on the beach at some point. But whereas most people's \"handwriting\" is washed away, one super-rich Arab sheikh has ensure that his graffiti will last a little longer. Hamad Bin Hamdan Al Nahyan, 63, has scrawled his name in sand on an island he owns with letters so big that they be seen from space. The word \"HAMAD\" measures 1,000 meters high and is a staggering two miles long from the \"H\" to the \"D\" on the Al Futaisi Island. And rather than allow the writing to be washed away by the ocean, the letters actually form waterways that absorb the encroaching tide. The ruler's name is even visible on Google's map service. Hamad dreamed up the idea and had his workmen work hard for weeks to craft the enormous piece of sand graffiti. It is not known how much it c...\n\nQ: Why does Hamad have his seven Mercedes-Benz500 SELs painted in different colors?", "options": ["Perhaps he hoped his cars were stored in a giant pyramid safely.", "In some ways he could make a very strange rainbow.", "Maybe he just wanted to show off his wealth.", "He is always interested in making his cars like these."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1339, "question": "Once a general manager wanted to test his people, who had come from all over India, about their values of life. He announced that in their folders , there is PVC pouch and in it there is a seed. When they return, they must put the seed in a pot with good soil and look after it very well. He would hold a competition at the next year's seminar and the best plants would be awarded suitably. Everyone did what was told to him. A year passed quickly. And the next year in a big hall, what a great scene! There were hundreds of pots and a great variety of plants-all except one. In this pot was soil, but no plant! The owner of the pot was standing quietly and feeling ashamed of himself. The general manager called him on the stage. He asked him what happened and he told him the truth. He planted the ...\n\nQ: What's the general manager's purpose of giving a seed to each of his employees?", "options": ["He wanted to get some beautiful plants.", "He wanted to improve his employees' planting skill", "He wanted to enrich his employees' life.", "He wanted to know whether his employees are honest."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1174, "question": "Rising levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere are a major cause of climate change, and now a new study has confirmed that atmospheric CO2is also affecting the ocean chemistry and potentially harming sea life. Montana State University scientist Robert Dore has been researching the water in the Pacific Ocean for almost two decades. We've been going to the same spot in the Pacific Ocean, and we try and characterize long-term change in the open ocean environment. And one of the key things that we measure is CO2levels. And we've been able to record this increasing quantity of atmospheric CO2into the ocean. Scientists expected that as atmospheric CO2increased, more and more of the carbon dioxide would be absorbed into the ocean, affecting the chemical balance of the sea water, with a potenti...\n\nQ: What can be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Sea Life Facing Danger", "Scientist Researching Seawater", "Oceans Becoming More Acidic", "Climate Change Affecting Seawater"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1013, "question": "BEIJING--Seven prestigious universities in China announced Sunday that they would begin using the same independent exam --besides the national one --to test students hoping to gain entrance to them in 2011. The seven are Peking University, Beihang University, Beijing Normal University, Nankai University, Fudan University, Xiamen University and Hong Kong University. Students who want to gain entrance to any of the seven universities will only have to sit one independent exam, according to the joint announcement. \"This will help lighten the students' load, otherwise they must take several exams for different universities ,\"said the announcement. Passing the exam could result in more than one interview chance, giving the students more opportunities to choose their favorite universities. China...\n\nQ: If students want to be admitted to the seven prestigious universities, they can  _  .", "options": ["only pass the interview.", "only take the national exam.", "only take the independent exam.", "either take the national exam or take the independent exam."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3454, "question": "It was a physical class. But it was nothing like previous ones -- the class was \"attended\" by over 60 million students across China, and the teacher was not even on the planet: she was 340 kilometers above the earth. \"Hello, everyone. I'm Wang Yaping. I'll host your lecture today.\" Smiling to the camera, Wang, China's second female astronaut, started her video class on June 20 on board the Tiangong-1 space station. To show how Newton's Laws work in space, Wang and her fellow astronauts used simple items like balls and spinning tops. The highlight of the lecture was when Wang _ using a metal ring, something that only happens in zero gravity, where the surface tension of water is much higher than it is on the earth. She then took it a step further by pouring more water onto the film and turn...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements can be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Teaching from the Sky.", "Teaching on Physics.", "Teaching Experiments.", "Teaching by an Astronaut."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1253, "question": "Sons who have fond childhood memories of their fathers are more likely to be emotionally stable in the face of day-to-day stresses, according to psychologists who studied hundreds of adults of all ages. \"As our study shows, fathers do play a unique and important role in the mental health of their children much later in life,\" psychology professor Melanie Mallers of California State University said. For this study, 912 adult men and women between the ages of 25 and 74 completed short daily telephone interviews about that day's experiences over an eight-day period. The interviews focused on the participants' psychological and emotional distress (i.e.whether they were nervous, sad, etc.) and if they had experienced any stressful events that day. The participants were also required to answer q...\n\nQ: What can be concluded from the passage?", "options": ["Parent-child relationships have a lasting effect on children.", "Adults with good childhood relationships with their parents are sure to be happy.", "The mother-child relationships is more important than the father-child one.", "The quality of parent-child relationships determines how people handle stress as adults."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 521, "question": "A recent online poll asked kids what they hated most about school. \"Classes are boring\" came in first. \"Too much homework\" was a close second. Since all activities remain interesting for only so long, too much homework can lead to ennui. So, why are some kids getting homework overload? Teachers give two reasons. First, they say, the government now requires schools to meet higher-than-ever achievement goals for students. If students don' t succeed, the school faces punishment. Second, many parents want their children to be able to get into the best colleges and universities. These parents believe homework is a way to ensure that students are learning as much as possible. People who favor homework argue that it can have many beneficial effects. They claim it can help students develop good st...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT a negative effect of too much homework?", "options": ["Kids have little time to do leisure activities.", "There is a lack of sleeping time.", "The chances of learning other skills are lost.", "Kids are under pressure from their parents."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1291, "question": "You may think that light pollution isn't something extraordinarily important. You may believe that every other type of pollution has a larger impact on the environment than light pollution does. But light pollution is serious. Light pollution, or \"sky glow\", is the glow you can see at night above cities and towns. Light pollution is a problem that has been accompanying man ever since he started his first fire some 15,000 years ago. Light pollution is the light that comes from streetlights, buildings, parking lots and any other source of light that is reflected or directed into the atmosphere. Urban light pollution means that one-fifth of the world's population can no longer see the Milky Way with the naked eye . Many city kids, even if they did look through the orange smog above their head...\n\nQ: All the following statements are false EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["Light pollution does not have as large an import on the earth as other types of pollution do", "Light pollution exists everywhere on the eafth", "People in some parts of the world cannot see the Milky Way with their naked eyes as a result of light pollution", "Loght pollution came into existence with modem technology"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 653, "question": "Lee Ann Laraway has polio and is not able to move very much. Most things are out of reach for her. Jeannie, a Labrador retriever, acts as her arms and legs. Jeannie understands 72 or more different commands. On a shopping trip, she can get money for Lee Ann at the bank or candies at the store. She can pay the cashier and get change back. Jeannie brings things to Lee Ann and puts them in her lap. Jeannie was trained at a place called Canine Companions for Independence, located on twelve acres of land in Santa Rosa (California). The land was donated by the cartoonist Charles Shultz. \"We train four different types of dogs here,\" said Ken Kirsh, a dog trainer there. \"Hearing dogs, service dogs, skilled companion dogs, and facility dogs.\" Trainers work with Labrador retrievers and golden retrie...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Dogs are helpful to people", "Four kinds of dogs", "Jeannie, a very clever dog", "How to train working dogs"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 95, "question": "Owning a smartphone may not be as smart as you think.They may let you surf the Internet,listen to music and snap photos wherever you are...but they also turn you into a workaholic,it seems.A study suggests that,by giving you access to emails at all times.the all-singing.all-dancing mobile phone adds as much as two hours to your working day. Researchers found that Britons work an additional 460hours a year on average as they are able to respond to emails on their mobiles.The study by technology retailer Pixmania,reveals the average UK working day is between nine and ten hours,but a further two hours is spent responding to or sending work emails,or making work calls.Almost one in ten admits spending up to three hours outside their normal working day checking work emails.Some workers confess ...\n\nQ: The text is probably taken from  _  .", "options": ["a scientific report", "a financial report", "a newspaper", "a literary journal"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2090, "question": "The percentage of districts that require elementary schools to teach physical education increased, to 93% last year from 83% in 2000. But just 4% of elementary schools, 8% of middle schools and 2% of high schools provided physical education each school day, as is recommended by the disease control agency. One-fifth of schools did not require physical education at all. In 2004, Congress passed a law requiring each school district to develop a \"wellness policy\" to promote the students' health by setting goals for nutrition education and physical activity. Those policies are just now taking effect, and some school administrators predict that the next survey will show more marked improvements. Some schools have set out to place health education on the same requirement with academics. In Los An...\n\nQ: To improve the health of the students, the school should have   _  .", "options": ["daily exercise for more than an hour", "daily exercise and proper eating habits", "good healthy eating", "much exercise"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3028, "question": "You've probably heard of the expression \"A leopard can't change its spots.\" This, of course, is true of leopards. But isn't it true of people? Can people change themselves? Are we humans just creatures of habits? Do we not have any control over our actions and habits? One guy said, \"Bad habits are like a comfortable bed. They're easy to get into, but hard to get out of.\" Someone else said, \"The chains of habits are too small to feel until they're too strong to break.\" So breaking the mould of our bad habits takes effort. Habits are like the roads we take through our life every day. The problem is that not every road takes us where we need to go. Actually, our routes through life often become our ruts in life. We end up stuck in them and find it hard to dig ourselves out. That's why we must...\n\nQ: The author's attitude towards changing one's bad habits is  _  .", "options": ["doubtful", "optimistic", "negative", "indifferent"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 379, "question": "Two thieves came to a house to steal something. They dug a hole in the wall of the house. There lived many mice in the house. The woman in the house saw a mouse crawl into the house in the moonlight. \"Look! In comes one,\" she said to the man in the house. The thief was so frightened that he hurriedly crawled out of the house and said to the one waiting outside, \"She found me when I was just in.\" But the thief outside didn't believe him, so he said, \"Let us try to crawl into the house together.\" At that time two mice happened to crawl into the house, too. The woman saw the mice and shouted, \"In come two, catch them!\" The two thieves were terribly frightened. The man in the house said, \"You saw them come in but where are they? I will catch them tonight.\" The two thieves started running away ...\n\nQ: \"  _  \"is the best title for this passage.", "options": ["Two Clever Thieves", "Terrible Mice", "Hit the Mark by a Fluke", "A Clever Coupe"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2103, "question": "Believe it or not, there're always some people who like staying up too late. However, sleeping early can bring us many benefits. 1. Healthy heart. Staying up late in the night is a way to hurt your body with high blood pressure and cholesterol . These are the risks associated with the heart. 2. Reduce stress. A peaceful sleep in the night relieves physical and mental stress. It relaxes the body and mind. With insufficient sleep you're risking your health with heart attacks and other diseases. 3. Improve memory. Sleeping early lets your mind arrange the thoughts well. Waking up early with a fresh mind will regain all of it. 4. Protect you from diseases. By sleeping late in the night you're only stressing yourself, which will increase the blood pressure and cholesterol levels. So sleep early...\n\nQ: What kind of sleep can relieve the physical and mental stress?", "options": ["A peaceful sleep.", "An insufficient sleep.", "A continuous sleep.", "An inadequate sleep."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1599, "question": "One day about 30 years ago, a 2 year-old Chinese boy in Shenyang was watching a Tom and Jerry cartoon on TV. Tom the cat began to play the piano. The music was to beautiful that the boy fell in love with it at once. This little boy was Lang Lang - one of today's great pianists. Lang Lang began to play the piano at 3. By the age of 5, the had won fist place in Shenyang's piano competition and performed his first public recital . People were shocked by his perfect performance and thought he was a real talent. From that time on, playing on the global stage became the dream of Lang Lang and his parents. To help him much closer to his dream, when Lang was 9, his father quit his job and went with Lang to Beijing to help his son study piano. There, Lang did not receive the praise that he had rece...\n\nQ: What happened to Lang Lang when he was in Bejing?", "options": ["He got more praises from others", "He damaged his hands.", "He had difficulty in making progress", "He lost his talent in piano"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 83, "question": "The best selling children's book, Pipilu Sending You 100 Lives, has been adapted into a homonymous play that will be put on for the first time next March and tour around 50 cities in China. The book was adapted by the Hangzhou based Star Dream Factory. \"We don't want to descend to the average children's dramas that are overly eager to please the kids,\" said Huang Qin, director of Star Dream Factory. \"We want to provide something practically useful and mystically entertaining.\" The original book by Chinese children's book writer Zheng Yuanjie focuses on safety tips for kids. With Zheng's usual _ and simplicity, the book avoids sugar-coating reality. Instead, it illustrates the potential dangers in everyday life and provides possible solutions. Zheng recalled that when he saw his new-born ba...\n\nQ: The purpose of the passage is to  _  ?", "options": ["introduce a play to remind children of the importance of safety", "introduce a book and its homonymous play to the readers", "tell the readers how to keep safe", "tell the readers how important safety is"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1813, "question": "A 13-year-old American boy on Saturday became the youngest climber to conquer Mount Everest, the world's highest mountain. Jordan Romero from Big Bear, California, climbed up the 8,850-meter summit from the Tibetan side. On the same day, a Nepali man, Apa Sherpa, broke his own world record of climbing Everest when he reached the summit for the twentieth time. Apa Shepa's team set off from Nepal's capital, Kathmandu, last month, heading for the base camp on the Chinese side of the mountain. \"The team has just called in and believe that they are standing on top of Mt. Everest,\" Romero's blog said. \"Their dreams have now come true. Everyone is happy.\" The climbing has put Romero one step closer to reaching his goal of climbing the highest mountains on all seven continents . \"It is just a goal...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that Romero   _  .", "options": ["is the first teenager to conquer Mr. Everest", "climbed Mr. Everest without the help of local guides", "still has two peaks to conquer in order to hit his goal", "is supported by his father"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2721, "question": "Google Works Miracles Google(www.Google.com) is a daily miracle to millions of people. If the Internet had only this very fast search engine, it would have justified its existence many times over. It is the most popular search engine on the web with a 54% market share, ahead of Yahoo! You type almost anything, however unclear, into the space provided and in a second it has come up with hundreds of references. If knowledge is power, then Google commands the gateway. Yahoo Becomes Giant Yahoo(www.yahoo.com) was the first wonder of the web, and in many respects, it still is. It started in January 1994 when two California graduate students, Jerry Yang and David Filo, started compiling a database of links, mainly for their personal use. But well before the end of the year, it had become recogni...\n\nQ: What is Google used mainly for?", "options": ["Commanding the gateway.", "Searching for information.", "Storing reference books.", "Providing extra space."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 369, "question": "Every few years, two groups carry out a study of how many Americans wash their hands after using the toilet. These groups are the American Society for Microbiology and the American Cleaning Institute, formerly the Soap and Detergent Association. There was good news in the latest study. Researchers found that eighty-five percent of adults washed their hands in public restrooms last month. That was the most since the studies began in 1996. Researchers visited restrooms at a baseball park in Atlanta and a science museum and aquarium in Chicago. They also visited two train stations in New York City and a large farmers' market in San Francisco. In all, they observed about six thousand adults, with females and males equal in number. The researchers found that seventy-seven percent of men and nin...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Hand washing is up in public restrooms in the US", "Americans like washing their hands so much", "Adults have their hands washed in public restrooms", "Why hand washing never enjoys popularity in the US"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2338, "question": "Whales live in the ocean, but they are not fish. They are warm-blooded mammals and must have air to breathe. The babies are born alive and drink milk from the mother's body. It took millions of years for the whale to develop as it is today. Every spring groups of whales swim hundreds of kilometers to warm places to bear their young. Each group goes to the same place every year. The mothers take very good care of their babies. The fully grown whales are very gentle and playful with each other, and with humans. They \"talk\" to each other with a high noise that sounds beautiful. This\"talking\" can be heard for more than 300 kilometers in open waters. Yet humans kill over a hundred whales a day. They kill them to make whale oils and a lot of other things. Killing them is a modern business with m...\n\nQ: A commonly mistaken belief is that    _   .", "options": ["whales are mammals", "whales must have air to breathe", "whales' babies drink milk", "whales are fish"], "answer": 3}]